BRADLY CHRISTENSEN

Monmouth, Oregon | 425-985-5459 | bradchristensen755@gmail.com

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Languages: C#, Javascript, HTML, LINQ, HTML, CSS, SQL

Frameworks / Tools: Git from command line, Visual Studio, ASP .NET, MVC,

Pivotal Tracker (Epics/User Stories), Azure, SQL Server

EXPERIENCE

Fall 2019 – Spring 2020

Western Oregon University - Senior Project Program

- · Worked with Agile Practices, using 2-week Sprints.
- Practiced Git from the command line for version control.
- · Used continuous deployment via Azure Webservices.
- Produced a shippable product at the end of each sprint, until the end of the year. (https://github.com/brad7555/SeniorProject)

Fall 2014 – Fall 2017

Football Player – Western Oregon University

- · 4 Year starter, 33 career starts.
- \cdot Learned valuable lessons in leadership and being a part of a team as well as hard work.
- · 2017 All-GNAC Team

EDUCATION

2017 - 2020

Western Oregon University, Monmouth, OR

B.S Computer Science

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a person who stutters. I have stuttered for my entire life and have worked extremely hard to get where I am at today. Through all of the hard times stuttering has brought on me, I have learned a lot about my ability to persevere and keep attacking hard situations consistently. I am currently working on my speech frequently. I see a speech pathologist 3 times a week and have made some great improvements over the past year. Conversations

are still hard situations for me, so interviews can be incredibly stressful for me. I ask that you don't try to finish my sentences and be patient. Stuttering doesn't define who I am, but it has made me the person that I am today. It has made me patient and understanding with every single person that I meet and talk to.

If you want any addition information, or just want to learn about stuttering, you can visit https://westutter.org/